<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>off_gallery.at</title>
  <subtitle>offgallery_graz - Nachrichten und Einladungen</subtitle>
  <link href="https://offgallery.at/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="https://offgallery.at/"/>
  <updated>2020-01-17T20:00:00+01:00</updated>
  <id>https://offgallery.at/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Anastasija Georgi, Erika Petrić, Heinz Wittenbrink</name>
    <email>info@offgallery.at</email>
  </author>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Vernissage: Liminal – A journey through the Albanian landscape</title>
    <link href="https://offgallery.at/news/liminal-a-journey-through-the-albanian-landscape/"/>
    <updated>2020-01-17T20:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>https://offgallery.at/news/liminal-a-journey-through-the-albanian-landscape/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Liminal - A journey through the Albanian landscape in still images&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AUSSTELLUNGSDAUER: 17.01. - 06.02.2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ÖFFNUNGSZEITEN: DI-DO 15:00 - 18:00&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(English below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Liminal - A journey through the Albanian landscape in still images&amp;quot; ist Teil eines Forschungsprojekts von &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/saimir-kristo-b08a404a/&quot; title=&quot;Saimir Kristo | LinkedIn&quot;&gt;Saimir Kristo&lt;/a&gt; und &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sonia-jojic-b5b00038/?originalSubdomain=al&quot; title=&quot;Sonia Jojic | LinkedIn&quot;&gt;Sonia Jojic&lt;/a&gt;. Es wird gerade von der &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.universitetipolis.edu.al/?q=en&quot; title=&quot;Universiteti Polis&quot;&gt;Polis University&lt;/a&gt; Tirana publiziert.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Die Fotografien betonen die Ambiguität der Landschaftsdarstellung. Sie erscheint auf den ersten Blick idyllisch, enthält aber dissoziative Elemente: Bunker in einer Vielzahl von Formen und Gestalten. Die kognitive Dissonanz schafft Raum für Fragen und Überraschungen.
Kreative Interventionen der Nutzer dieser Gebäude – viele von ihnen sehr humorvoll – zeigen, wie widerstandsfähig das Leben tatsächlich ist und bleiben kann.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Anwesenheit der AutorInnen eröffnen wir die Ausstellung am 17. Januar 2020 um 19:00 Uhr. Auf die Eröffnung folgen ein kurzes Künstlergespräch und eine offene Diskussion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Liminal - A journey through the Albanian landscape in still images&amp;quot; is part of a research project by Saimir Kristo, Sonia Jojic and Joana Dhiamandi. It is currently being published by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.universitetipolis.edu.al/?q=en&quot; title=&quot;Universiteti Polis&quot;&gt;Polis University&lt;/a&gt; Tirana&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The photographs shown in this exhibition emphasize the ambiguity of landscape representation. At first glance it appears idyllic, but it contains dissociative elements: Bunkers in a variety of shapes and forms. The cognitive dissonance creates a space for questions and surprise.
Creative interventions by the appropriators of these buildings - many of them very humorous - show how resilient life really is and can remain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the presence of the authors we will open the exhibition on 17 January 2020 at 19:00. The opening will be followed by a short artist talk and an open discussion.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
